mydd.com 2007-12-09

# MyDD :: Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy 

**Security**

The servers that house this site are maintained in a manner that safeguards the information in our databases effectively.

**Collecting Information**

Unless you voluntarily provide us with any personal information, such as your e-mail address, this site does not place "cookies" to collect personal information about you without your knowledge.

When you visit our site, we collect the following information: The name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account). The date and time you access our site. The Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site or the Internet address of the computer used to link to our site. This information is used for Site Management purposes only. Our computer system uses software programs to create summary statistics using this information so we know, for instance, the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest to viewers, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

Unless you choose to provide such information, we do not collect or maintain personal information about you when you visit our site. If you send us an E-mail message or complete a web form containing personal information, we collect and store the personal information which you choose to provide, such as your mailing address, e-mail address and the content of any request for information or any comments you may have.

**Use of information**

If you choose to provide any personal information, such as your email, we may use that information to contact you. We do not share the information our visitors provide with other organizations.

Users can change their data in the database or unsubscribe at any point.
